Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology records, 1900-2017
Cornell University, New York State College of Human Ecology records,
- Series II. Dean's Files
  - B. Francille Firebaugh (1988-1999)
    - 3) Subject Files and Correspondence (box 114 contains computer disks of correspondence (1980-1996)created in WordPerfect formatted for an IBM compatible computer)
      - Health Administration, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Health Administration Program-Human Service Studies- Review Process, 1985-1987 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Sloan Program in Health Administration, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Health Administration, 1990-1993 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Health Program, 1980's (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Health Administration Graduate Program, 1980's (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Nursing Program, 1978-1979 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - College Health Committee-Report of Feasibility Study, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - Summer Research Opportunities for Minority Students, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 22)
      - Minority Student Summer Research, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 23)
      - Summer Research Fellowships-Minority Students, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 24)
      - Minority Student Summer Research Program, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 25)
      - Minority Education Advisory Council (Box 55, Folder 26)
      - Minority Graduate and Professorial Education Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 55, Folder 27)
      - Minority Fellowships (Box 55, Folder 28)
      - Recruitment- Graduate (Box 55, Folder 29)
      - Graduate Education- SUNY Review (Box 55, Folder 30)
      - Minority Recruitment (Box 55, Folder 31)
      - Minority Recruitment, 1980-1989 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Minority Faculty Crisis at Cornell, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Minority Recruitment-Event III, 1984-10-07-1984-10-08 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Minority Recruitment-Event II, 1983-10-16-1983-10-17 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Minority Recruitment- Event I, 1982-12-13 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Minority Recruitment at Cornell, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Common Learning Courses, 1982-1985 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Proposal for Ph.D. in Textiles (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Toward the year 2000-Marking the Dedication of the North Wing in MVR, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Northeast Home Economics Research Priorities Committee, 1986 and 1991 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Northeast Home Economics Research Priorities Committee, 1980's (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Northeast Home Economics Research Priorities Committee, 1980's (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Human Development and Family Studies- Doctoral Program in Developmental Psychology- State Review, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Human Development and Family Studies- Doctoral Program in Developmental Psychology- State Review, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Sloan Program in Health Services Administration- Accreditation Report, Volume I, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Sloan Program in Health Services Administration- Accreditation Report, Volume II, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Sloan Program in Health Services Administration- Accreditation Report, Volume II, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Social Work Program Evaluative Standard I (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Social Work Program Evaluative Standard I (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Graduate Education Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - HSS (Human Services Studies) 5 year Review, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - HSS (Human Services Studies) 5 year Review, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Department of Design and Environmental Analysis- Review, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Department of Design and Environmental Analysis- Review, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Department of Community Service Education Review (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - Field Study Review, 1981-04 (Box 56, Folder 26)
      - Morrison Report (Tenure and Promotion) (Box 56, Folder 27)
      - CEH (Consumer Economics and Housing) Department Review, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 28)
      - HDFS (Human Development and Family Studies) Department Review, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 29)
      - Design and Environmental Analysis Review, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 30)
      - Division Review- Nutritional Sciences, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - HSS (Human Service Studies) Overview, 1986-1987 (Box 56, Folder 32)
      - ACC-BUDGET- Annual Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - ACC-BUDGET-Annual Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - ACC-CORP-Rich's (Janet Dewart) (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - ACC-CORP- Rockefeller Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - ACC-EXPENSE- Travel- Cornell Club, 1991-1998 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - ACC-FUND-Albany Contacts, 1995-1998 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - ACC-FUND- Albany (Francille Firebaugh), 1993-1998 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - ADMIN-ACADEMIC- Future of College, 1995-1998 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - ADMIN-ACADEMIC- Future of College, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - ADMIN-COLLEGES-CALS-USDA-Catherine Woteki Visit, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - ADMIN-COLLEGES-SCIENCE and TECHNOLOGY STUDIES, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - ADMIN-COLLEGES-AGRICULTURE and LIFE SCIENCES (CALS), 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - ADMIN-COLLEGES-AGRICULTURE and LIFE SCIENCES (CALS), 1995-1996 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEE-AFFIRMATIVE ACTION (general), 1998 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEE-AFFIRMATIVE ACTION (general), 1994-1997 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEE-AFFIRMATIVE ACTION Sub-Committee on Faculty Recruitment, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEE-AFFIRMATIVE ACTION Sub-Committee on Graduate Student Recruitment, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEE-LIFE COURSE STUDIES SEARCH COMMITTEE, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEE-LIFE COURSE STUDIES SEARCH COMMITTEE, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - ADMIN-COUNCILS-ADVISORY COUNCIL, 1998-09-24-1998-09-25 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - ADMIN-COUNCILS-ADVISORY COUNCIL, 1998-04-29-1998-04-30 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - ADMIN-DEPT-DNS-CHAIR SEARCH, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - ADMIN-DEPT-DNS-CHAIR SEARCH, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 23)
      - ADMIN-DEPT-PAM-CHAIR SEARCH, 1996-1997 (Box 57, Folder 24)
      - ADMIN-DEPT-PAM-SOCIAL WORK CORRESPONDENCE, 1996-2000 (Box 57, Folder 25)
      - ADMIN-DEPT-PAM-SOCIAL WORK CORRESPONDENCE, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 26)
      - ADMIN-DEPART-PAM-SOCIAL WORK OPTION, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 27)
      - ADMIN-DEPART-PAM-SOCIAL WORK OPTION, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 28)
      - ADMIN-DEPART-PAM-SOCIAL WORK TASK FORCE, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 29)
      - ADMIN-DEPART-PAM-SOCIAL WORK TASK FORCE, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 30)
      - ADMIN-INTERNATIONAL-INTERNATIONAL YEAR OF THE FAMILY, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 31)
      - ADMIN-ORG-NASULGC- Budget Committee, folder 1, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - ADMIN-ORG-NASULGC- Budget Committee, folder 2, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - ADMIN-ORG-NASULGC- Commission on the Urban Agenda, 1995-1997 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - ADMIN-ORG-NASULGC- Testimony-USDA, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - ADMIN-POLICY-Policy Persepectives: "Supporting Children in an Era of Welfare Reform; "Community-Based Health Planning"; "Making Social Indicators Useful for Policy and Program Management in New York State"; Healthy Communities: Concepts and Collaboration Tools", 1996-1998 (Box 105, Folder 27)
      - ADMIN-STATE-SUNY, folder 1, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - ADMIN-STATE-SUNY, folder 2, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - ADMIN-STATE-SUNY-RESOURCE ALLOCATION MODEL (RAM), 1998-1999 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - ADMIN-STATE-SUNY-RESOURCE ALLOCATION MODEL (RAM), 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - ADMIN-STATE-STATUTORY DEANS, folder 1, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - ADMIN-STATE-STATUTORY DEANS, folder 2, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - ADMIN-STATE-STATUTORY DEANS, folder 3, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - ADMIN-STATE-STATUTORY DEANS, folder 4, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - ADMIN-STATE-STATUTORY DEANS, folder 5, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - ADMIN-TASK FORCE-Take Our Children to Work, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - ADMIN-UNIV-ACADEMIC DEANS, folder 1, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - ADMIN-UNIV-ACADEMIC DEANS, folder 2, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - ADMIN-UNIV-CORNELL ABROAD COSTS, 1993-1998 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - ADMIN-UNIV-Class of 1998 Senior Survey (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - DEANS CORRESPONDENCE, A-B (Francille Firebaugh and Patsy Brannon), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - DEANS CORRESPONDENCE, C-D (Francille Firebaugh and Patsy Brannon), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - DEANS CORRESPONDENCE, E-G (Francille Firebaugh and Patsy Brannon), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - DEANS CORRESPONDENCE, H-J (Francille Firebaugh and Patsy Brannon), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - DEANS CORRESPONDENCE, K-L (Francille Firebaugh and Patsy Brannon), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - DEANS CORRESPONDENCE, M (Francille Firebaugh and Patsy Brannon), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - DEANS CORRESPONDENCE, N-P (Francille Firebaugh and Patsy Brannon), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - DEANS CORRESPONDENCE, R (Francille Firebaugh and Patsy Brannon), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - DEANS CORRESPONDENCE, S-T (Francille Firebaugh and Patsy Brannon), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - DEANS CORRESPONDENCE, V-Z (Francille Firebaugh and Patsy Brannon), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY-CaRDI, 1998-1999 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY-ACADEMIC DEANS, 2000-2001 (Box 59, Folder 14-18)
      - ADMIN-STATE-SUNY, folder 3, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 19-20)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEES-APPLIED GERONLOLOGY RESEARCH, 1995- (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEES-ALICE COOK FUND COMMITTEE, 1999- (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEES-ARCHIVES, 1995-1998 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEES-INTERNATIONAL STUDIES REVIEW, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEES-CIPA PROVOST'S COUNCIL, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEES-CIPA, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - ADMIN-CORRESPONDENCE-OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY, 1991-1996 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - ADMIN-CORRESPONDENCE-PENN STATE UNIVERSITY, 1993-1995 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - ADMIN-CORRESPONDENCE-UNITED NATIONS UNIVIVERSITY (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - ADMIN-COUNCIL and BOARDS- HUMAN RESOURCE DEVELOPMENT COUNCIL, 1993- (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - ADMIN-COUNCIL and BOARDS-OFFICE OF ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - ADMIN-DEPTS-(CIT)-ADMIN-COMPUTER SCIENCE, 1994- (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - ADMIN-DEPTS-(PAM)-MEWAR,MANESH (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - ADMIN-DEPTS-MEDIA SERVICES-ELECTRONIC TECHNOLOGY, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - ADMIN-OFFICE OF COMPUTING AND STATISTICAL CONSULTING (OCSC), 1984-1996 (Box 105, Folder 49)
      - ADMIN-INTERNATIONAL-ASIA PROGRAM (SEAO), 1995 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - ADMIN-INTERNATIONAL-INDIA, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - ADMIN-INTERNATIONAL-INTERNATIONAL STUDIES, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - ADMIN-INTERNATIONAL-UNIVERSIDAD DELROSARIO, COLUMBIA (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - ADMIN-INTERNATIONAL ACTIVITIES INVENTORY, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 25)
      - ADMIN-ORGANIZATIONS-AHEA-PUBLICATIONS, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - ADMIN-ORGANIZATIONS-MENTORSHIP WORK, 1993-1995 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - ADMIN-AWID, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - ADMIN-ORGANIZATIONS-KAPPA OMICRON NU EDIT. COMMITTEE, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 22)
      - ADMIN-ORGANIZATIONS-KON FORUM PUBLICATION, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 23)
      - ADMIN-ORGANIZATIONS-PKP JOURNAL-NATIONAL FORUM, 1996- (Box 60, Folder 24)
      - ADMIN-STATE-SUNY BOARD OF TRUSTEES, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 25)
      - ADMIN-STATE-SUNY CHANCELLOR, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 26)
      - ADMIN-STATE-SUNY COUNCIL OF PRESIDENTS, 1995-1996 (Box 60, Folder 27)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY-CORNELL ALUMNI UNIVERSITY, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 28)
      - ALU-ALUMNI DEPARTMENT-ALUMNI SEMINARS UPSTATE, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 29)
      - ALU-ALUMNI EPARTMENT-REUNION, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 30)
      - ALU-DEVELOPMENT-ANONYMOUS DONOR, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 31)
      - ALU-DEVELOPMENT-WOMEN AND BUSINESS, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 32)
      - ALU-DEVELOPMENT-WOMEN AND PHILANTHROPY, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 33)
      - ALU-DEVELOPMENT-ENDOWED CHAIRS-CHALLENGE MEINIG, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 34)
      - ALU-DEVELOPMENT-ENDOWED CHAIRS-JACOB GOULD SCHURMAN, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - COOPERATIVE EXTENSION-FARM BILL, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 36)
      - COOPERATIVE EXTENSION-PROGRAM DEVELOPMENT AND EVALUATION, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - 4. Chairs and Deans Meetings
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1994-01-1994-06 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1994-08-1994-12 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1996-01-1996-07 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1996-08-1996-12 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 17)
        Spring
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 11)
        Fall
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 21)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 22)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 19)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 20)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - C. Patsy Brannon (1999-2004)
    - 1. Policies, Committees, etc.
      - ACC Budgets- Annual Reports (folder 1), 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - ACC Budgets- Annual Reports (folder 2), 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - ACC Budgets- Budget, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - ADMIN-Corespondence-(NCI) Gerry Grenham, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - ADMIN-Councils and Boards-Advisory Council, 2000-10-05-2000-10-06 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - ADMIN-Councils and Boards-Advisory Council, 2000-03-30-2000-03-31 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - ADMIN-Councils and Boards-Advisory Council, 2000-10-05-2000-10-06 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - ADMIN-Councils and Boards-Advisory Council, 1999-10-28-1999-10-29 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - ADMIN-DEPARTMENTS-(DNS), Filling faculty positions, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - ADMIN-DEPARTMENTS-(DNS), Filling faculty positions, 2001-2002 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - ADMIN-DEPARTMENTS-(PAM), Consumer Policy Position, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - ADMIN-DEPARTMENTS-(PAM), Extension/Outreach Position, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - ADMIN-DEPARTMENTS-(PAM), Mixed Methods, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - ADMIN-DEPARTMENTS-(PAM), Social Welfare Evaluation Position, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - ADMIN-Faculty Search Procedures, 1998-2001 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - ADMIN-STATE-SUNY (folder 1), 2000 (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - ADMIN-STATE-SUNY (folder 2), 2000 (Box 62, Folder 16)
      - ADMIN-COUNCILS and BOARDS, President's Council, 2000-2001 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - ADMIN-COUNCILS and BOARDS, President's Council, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - ADMIN-INTERNATIONAL, Japan Kyoritsu University, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - ADMIN-INTERNATIONAL, Japan Kyoritsu University-including photographs, 1997-1998 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - ADMIN-INTERNATIONAL, Japan Kyoritsu University - Agreement, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - ADMIN-STATE, Statutory Deans' Meetings, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - ADMIN-STATE, Statutory Deans' Meetings, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - ADMIN-STATE, Statutory Deans' Meetings, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - ADMIN-STATE, Statutory Deans' Meetings, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - ADMIN-COMMITTEE, 1998-12-1999-08 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - ADMIN-STATE, SUNY, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Academic Deans, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Academic Deans, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Academic Programs (Ehrenberg), 1995-1997 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Campus Compact, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, CaRDI, 1999-2001 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY,CIIFAD, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Folder 12)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY,CIIFAD - External Review, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 38)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Humanities Report (CU), 1998 (Box 75, Folder 13)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Center for Policy Research (CCPR), 2000 (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Center for Policy Research (CCPR), 2000 (Box 75, Folder 15)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Center for Policy Research (CCPR), 2000 (Box 75, Folder 16)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Project 2000 (Y2K), 1996 (Box 75, Folder 17)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Kyoto Protocol, 1997-2003 (Box 122, Folder 28)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Genomics Initiative, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 33-34)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Genomics Initiative, 2000-2004 (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, President's Council of Cornell Women (PCCW), childcare, 1998-2002 (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - ADMIN-TASK FORCES, (CHE) Admissions, 1993-1995 (Box 75, Folder 18)
      - ADMIN-TASK FORCES, Biological Sciences, 1997-1998 (Box 75, Folder 19)
      - ADMIN-TASK FORCES, Computing and Informational Science, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 20)
      - ADMIN-TASK FORCES, Leadership (Cornell), 1998 (Box 75, Folder 21)
      - ADMIN-TASK FORCES, Research Futures, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 22)
      - ADMIN-TASK FORCES, Residential Communities Implementation Plan, 1996-1997 (Box 75, Folder 23)
      - ADMIN-TASK FORCES, Strategic Planning (CU), 1993-1994 (Box 75, Folder 24)
      - ADMIN-UNIVERSITY, Vice President Committee on Sociology, 1996-1998 (Box 75, Folder 25)
      - Policy Perspectives Seminar Steering Committee, 1995-1998 (Box 101, Folder 15)
      - Policy Perspectives Seminar Summary Reports, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - Policy Perspectives Seminar Summary Reports, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - Policy Perspectives Seminar Summary Reports, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - Policy Perspectives Seminar Summary Reports, 1998 (Box 101, Folder 18)
      - Policy Perspectives Summary Reports, 1999 (Box 101, Folder 19)
      - Policy Perspectives Seminar Series, 2000-2001, 2004 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - 2. Trip Files
      - P. Brannon Arlington, Texas, 1999-02-03-1999-02-06 (Box 80, Folder 20)
      - Albany, New York FLDC - reception and meet with government officials, 1999-04-08-1999-04-10 (Box 80, Folder 21)
      - Silver Spring to Ithaca and back, 1999-05-05-1999-05-09 (Box 80, Folder 22)
      - New York City, 1999-05-14 (Box 80, Folder 23)
      - Ithaca to Silver Springs and back, 1999-06-13-1999-06-14 (Box 80, Folder 24)
      - Washington, DC NIH Study Group, 1999-06-13-1999-06-18 (Box 80, Folder 25)
      - Chicago, IL Institute of Food Technologists, 1999-07-23-1999-07-26 (Box 80, Folder 26)
      - Rochester, New York- NEAFCS - New York Affiliate, 1999-09-27 (Box 80, Folder 27)
      - Baltimore, MD (ASNS), 1999-09-11-1999-09-12 (Box 80, Folder 28)
      - San Francisco, CA NASULGC Annual Meeting, 1999-11-07-1999-11-09 (Box 80, Folder 29)
      - New York City-Cornell Cooperative Extension, Dinner with Donors, 1999-11-11-1999-11-14 (Box 80, Folder 30)
      - Chicago, IL (NASULGC legislative), 2000-01-16-2000-01-17 (Box 80, Folder 31)
      - New York City-President's Circle, HEAA Board, CACO, 2000-01-26-2000-01-28 (Box 80, Folder 32)
      - Washington, DC - BoHS/Federal Relations (Box 80, Folder 33)
      - Austin, Texas - External Review for University of Texas, 2000-01-31 (Box 80, Folder 34)
      - Albany, New York (Charles McClintock), 2000-02-01-2000-02-04 (Box 80, Folder 35)
      - Binghamton, New York Cornell Club of the Southern Tier, 2000-02-07-2000-02-08 (Box 80, Folder 36)
      - Washington, DC - NASULGC/Legislators/NIDDK Meetings, 2000-02-26 (Box 80, Folder 37)
      - San Diego/San Francisco, CA (Experimental Biology and Development), 2000-02-26-2000-03-03 (Box 80, Folder 38)
      - Chicago, IL FANSA, 2000-04-14-2000-04-23 (Box 80, Folder 39)
      - Beltsville, MD (Review of BHNRC), 2000-04-26 (Box 80, Folder 40)
      - Sacramento, CA - Review of UC Davis Graduate Program, 2000-05-03-2000-05-05 (Box 80, Folder 41)
      - Albany, New York (w/ Cutberto Garza), 2000-05-07-2000-05-09 (Box 80, Folder 42)
      - Washington, DC - CFERR Executive Committee Meeting, 2000-05-12 (Box 80, Folder 43)
      - New York City (Tower Club Dinner), 2000-05-16-2000-05-17 (Box 80, Folder 44)
      - Baltimore, MD - Maryland Commencement, 2000-05-18 (Box 80, Folder 45)
      - Board of Trustees and Commencement, 2000-05-26-2000-05-28 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - University of Maryland, 2000-06-01 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Reunion, 2000-06-08-2000-06-11 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - New York City, Stony Brook, 2000-06-26-2000-06-28 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Cincinnati, Ohio - Research, 2000-06-29-2000-07-02 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - New York City and Washington, DC- Cornell University Council Administration Board, Weill, NIDDK, 2000-07-12-2000-07-14 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Washington, DC (FASEB and Hill), 2000-09-12-2000-09-15 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - New York City- PCCW, 2000-06-15-2000-06-17 (Box 81)
      - Baltimore, MD, 2000-10-22-2000-10-24 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Syracuse, New York- ACCEE Conference, 2000-10-25 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Washington, DC- NIDDK, 2000-11-01-2000-11-02 (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Santa Fe, NM- Lifelines, 2000-11-02-2000-11-05 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Washington, DC, Santa Fe, New Mexico and LA, 2000-10-28-2000-11-06 (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - San Antonio, Texas- NASULGC, 2000-11-10-2000-11-19 (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Cincinnati, Ohio- Research, 2000-11-29-2000-12-01 (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - Washington, DC- White House commission on Complementary and Alternative, 2000-12-03-2000-12-04 (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - New York City, SUNY, 2000-12-14 (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - Rochester, New York Founder's Day, 2001-01-13 (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - Chicago, Illinois, 2001-01-14 (Box 81, Folder 18)
      - Washington, DC- BoHS Federal Relations committee, 2001-01-23 (Box 81, Folder 19)
      - New York City, 2001-01-24 (Box 81, Folder 20)
      - Sarasota, Florida, 2001-01-25-2001-01-28 (Box 81)
      - New York City- Cornell University Administrative Board Meeting, Cornell University Council, 2001-02-07 (Box 81, Folder 21)
      - Washington, DC Legislative visits and centennial brief, 2001-02-25-2001-02-27 (Box 81, Folder 22)
      - Washington, DC FASEB and NAS Post Doc Convocation, 2001-03-01-2001-03-02 (Box 81, Folder 23)
      - Orlando, Florida, EB meetings, alumni/donor visits, 2001-03-31-2001-04-08 (Box 81, Folder 24)
      - Albany, New York SUNY Day, President's Meeting, 2001-03-05-2001-03-07 (Box 81, Folder 25)
      - Bethesda, MD DDK- C Subcommittee and Ratna Mukhejea Defense, 2001-04-12-2001-04-16 (Box 81, Folder 26)
      - New York City- Gala Centennial Celebration, 2001-04-20-2001-04-21 (Box 81, Folder 27)
      - Washington, DC CFERR Executive Committee, 2001-04-29-2001-04-30 (Box 81, Folder 28)
      - New York City Tower Club Dinner, 2001-05-11-2001-05-11 (Box 81, Folder 29)
      - West Coast Trip, 2001-05-15-2001-05-23 (Box 81, Folder 30)